Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - Early governance records, 1986 - 1998; F-177-1-18; 65 cm of textual records 3 photographs.
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], November 5, 1997, F-177-1-18-0-58 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], October 17, 1997, F-177-1-18-0-59 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], September 16, 1997, vol. 1, F-177-1-18-0-60 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], September 16, 1997, vol. 2, F-177-1-18-0-61 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], December 10, 1996, vol. 1, F-177-1-18-0-62 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], December 10, 1996, vol. 2, F-177-1-18-0-63 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], October 24, 1996, vol. 1, F-177-1-18-0-64 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
    - IGB [minutes and related papers], October 24, 1996, vol. 2, F-177-1-18-0-65 (Archival box - standard 177-73)
- Board of Governors records, 1995 - 2002; F-177-2; 2.50 m of textual records 26 photographs 88 negatives 1 contact sheet; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-177-2-1-0-11 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-177-2-1-0-12 Physical description: 21 photographs located in F-177-2-1-0-13 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-177-2-1-0-14; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors
  Established by the "Technical University of British Columbia Act" on December 5, 1997, the Board of Governors was the principal decison-making body at the University. It was composed of the Chancellor, the President, two teaching staff members, eight people appointed by the Lieutenant Governor in Council, two students, and one university employee who was not a teaching staff member. According to the Act, the Board was mandated to "approve strategic program and research directions and policies"; make decisions concerning TechBC programs and program areas; and provide reports to the appropriate Ministry as necessary. The Board was also responsible for appointing a President for the University. Its first meeting was on December 12, 1997. The Board had a number of standing committees; these were the Academic Planning Board, Audit Committtee, Business and Finance Committee, Executive Committee, Human Resources Committee, and Senior Compensation Committee. Other committees established by the Board were the University Review Committee and the Presidential Search Committee. In light of the Provincial Government's February 2002 decision to close TechBC, the Board began the process of dissolving its committees at its March 11, 2002 meeting. The final meeting of the Board took place on July 31, 2002.
  Series consists of records relating to the activities of the Board of Governors and its committees. Activities, events and topics documented include the composition, duties, responsibilities, and activities of the Board; meetings of the Board and its committees; the establishment of University budgets; University finances; Presidential recruitment; Presidential reports to the Board; human resources issues; and campus development.
  Records include terms of reference, minutes, agendas, and supporting papers; correspondence and reports; subject files; budgets and financial statements; working papers; reference manuals and policy statements; member lists; contracts; press releases; presentations; and photographs.
  Dickson, Ron; Watters, Jean; Armstrong, Gerry; Finnbogason, Jack; Paton, Arlene; Shilliday, Sharon
  - Administrative files, 1995 - 2002; F-177-2-1; 25 cm of textual records 26 photographs. 88 negatives. 1 contact sheet.
    Sub-series consists of administrative files relating to the composition and activities of the Board of Governors. Activities, events and topics documented include Board duties, responsibilities, and elections; appointments to the Board; Board member biographical information and photographs; hiring of the first President; the President's reports to the Board; the Committee of the Whole Discussion on Assessment of the President; correspondence and relations with the Ministry of Advanced Education, Training and Technology; early University planning; and the announcement and construction of the Surrey City Centre site. Records include correspondence, reports, subject files, reference manuals, policy statements, presentations, and photographs.
    - TechBC - early planning documents, 1996 - 1998; F-177-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - Committee of the Whole, 1995 - 1998; F-177-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - general correspondence, 1999 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - duties and responsibilities, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - governance information, 1995; F-177-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - insurance coverage, 1999; F-177-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Learner elections, October 26, 2001, F-177-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - elections, 1997 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - MAETT correspondence, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - orientation, November 20, 2000, F-177-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Photographs - [Board of Governors], 1999; F-177-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Photographs -[Tech One students / Surrey City Centre project announcement, 09/23/1999], F-177-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Photographs - [campus construction], 2000; F-177-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Photographs - [Jack Finnbogason / TechBC sign at Surrey Place], 2000; F-177-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Photographs - [TechBC people -various / Surrey City Centre project announcement, 09/23/1999 (negatives)], 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - small 177-68)
    - Board of Governors - potential board appointments, vol. 1, 2001 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - potential board appointments, vol. 2, 2001 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - President's approved expenses, 2000; F-177-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - President's updates, vol. 1, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - President's updates, vol. 2, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - Jean's updates to Board, 2001; F-177-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-74)
    - Board of Governors - provincial legislation, 1999; F-177-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - reference manual, November 2001, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - reference manual, November 2001, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - reference manual, November 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - reference manual, November 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - reference manual, November 2000, vol. 3, F-177-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board of Governors - personal data gathering form, 2000; F-177-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board Chair - Ron Dickson, 1996 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board Vice-Chair - Jack Finnbogason, 1996 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Tom Calvert, 1997; F-177-2-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Graham Rodwell, 1999; F-177-2-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Sharon Shilliday, 1997 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Nicky Sung, 1997 - 2002; F-177-2-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Honorio Todino, 2000; F-177-2-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Board member - Don Wright, 1998 - 2001; F-177-2-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Jude Brown, 2000; F-177-2-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Frank Karabotsos, 2001; F-177-2-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Ron Wakkary, 2000; F-177-2-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
  - Budget planning files, 1996 - 2001; F-177-2-2; 22 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to Tech BC budget preparation. Activities, events and topics documented include salary and budget determination; government funding; project statements; and meetings of the University Budget Committee and the Budget and Finance Committee. Records include budgets and financial statements; reports; working papers; minutes and supporting papers; and correspondence.
    Technical University of British Columbia. University Budget Committee; Technical University of British Columbia. Board of Governors. Business and Finance Committee
    - Budget information, 1996 - 1998; F-177-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - TUBC - December 13, 2001 - facilities budget, F-177-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Salary projections 2001/2002, F-177-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Spare copies - budget 2001/2002, F-177-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Cost centre heads - 2001/06/27 - 2001/2002 approved budget, F-177-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-75)
    - Budget 2001/2002 - external documents, F-177-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Miscellaneous budget documents 2000/2001, F-177-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - BandF Committee - land revenue fund meeting, June 6, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, May 16, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, May 7, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, April 25, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, April 17, 2002, 2001; F-177-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - 2001/2002 budget request package, March 15, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, March 14, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - 2001/2002 budget kick off meeting, March 12, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, February 26, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, February 6, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - The University Budget Committee meeting, January 16, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Revised 2000/01 budgets, sent January 18, 2001, F-177-2-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Approved budget 2001/2002 - working cupy, F-177-2-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Cost centre heads - September 25, 2000 - 2000/2001 approved budget, F-177-2-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Project statements: 2001/2002 budgets, vol. 1, F-177-2-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Project statements: 2001/2002 budgets, vol. 2, F-177-2-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Project statements: 2001/2002 budgets, vol. 3, F-177-2-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Board of Governors - budget insert, September 13, 2000, F-177-2-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-76)
    - Budget 2000/2001 - external documents, F-177-2-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - The University Budget Committee - budget update - July 17, 2000, F-177-2-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Cost centre heads - April 19, 2000 - 2000/20001 budget preparation, F-177-2-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - The University Budget Committee - information package- March 10, 2000, F-177-2-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Approved budget 2000/2001 - working copy, F-177-2-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - 1999/2000 approved budget, F-177-2-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - 1999/2000 budget correspondence, 1998 - 1999; F-177-2-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - 1999/2000 budget memos, F-177-2-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Budget - 1998/1999, F-177-2-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Budget - 1997/1998, F-177-2-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Budget - 1996/1997, F-177-2-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Budget process meeting, 1999; F-177-2-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
  - Board minutes and supporting papers, 1997 - 2002; F-177-2-3; 1.06 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of minutes and supporting papers relating to regular and in-camera meetings of the Board of Governors.
    The arrangement of files chronologically by the archivist is based on the original filing system, which was generally chronological.
    - Board of Governors, July 31, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors, July 23, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors, July 11, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors, July 5, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors, April 16, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 16, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, April 16, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 20, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 11, 2002, F-177-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors meeting, December 5, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, December 5, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-77)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 3, 2001, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 3, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 3, 2001, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, October 3, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, September 14, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, August 8. 2001, F-177-2-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 6, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 6, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-20.1 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, June 6, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 4, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, April 4, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, March 28, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-78)
    - Board of Governors meeting, February 7, 2001, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, February 7, 2001, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, February 7, 2001, F-177-2-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, November 29, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, November 29, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors tele conference, November 1, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 13, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 13, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, September 13, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, July 12, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, July 12, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, July 12, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - VP business and finance appointment information package, June 23, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-79)
    - Board of Governors meeting, May 24, 2000, vol. 1, 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Board of Governors meeting, May 24, 2000, vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-177-2-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, May 24, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Board of Governors, April 12, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Board of Governors in camera session, April 12, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, March 9, 2000, F-177-2-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999 [for 2000/03/09 in camera meeting], vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - TechBC's business case, September 3, 1999 [for 2000/03/09 in camera meeting], vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, March 10, 2002, vol. 1, 2000 - 2002; F-177-2-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, March 10, 2002, vol. 2, 2000 - 2002; F-177-2-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, March 10, 2002, vol. 3, 2000 - 2002; F-177-2-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 177-80)
    - Surrey City Centre project - formal agreements, March 10, 2002, vol. 4, 2000 - 2002; F-177-2-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, March 9, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, March 9, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, February 2, 2000, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, February 2, 2000, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, November 24, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, November 24, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, November 24, 1999 - Promotional items distributed, F-177-2-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 13, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 13, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 177-81)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 13, 1999, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, October 13, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 1, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 1, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, August 18, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, August 18, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 1999, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 1999, vol. 4, F-177-2-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 177-82)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 1999, vol. 5, F-177-2-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors - in camera meeting, June 2, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-70.1 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 21, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors in camera meeting, April 21, 1999, F-177-2-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 10, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 10, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 10, 1999, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-78 (Archival box - standard 177-83)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 4, F-177-2-3-0-79 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 5, F-177-2-3-0-80 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 28, 1999, vol. 6, F-177-2-3-0-81 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, December 7, 1998, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-82 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, December 7, 1998, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-83 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, October 28, 1998, F-177-2-3-0-84 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 15, 1998, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-85 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 15, 1998, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-86 (Archival box - standard 177-84)
    - Board of Governors meeting, September 15, 1998, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-87 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, June 18, 1998, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-88 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, May 28, 1998, F-177-2-3-0-89 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 23, 1998, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-90 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 23, 1998, vol. 2, F-177-2-3-0-91 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, April 23, 1998, vol. 3, F-177-2-3-0-92 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 19, 1998, F-177-2-3-0-93 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, March 5, 1998, F-177-2-3-0-94 (Archival box - standard 177-85)
    - Board of Governors meeting, January 26, 1998, vol. 1, F-177-2-3-0-95 (Archival box - standard 177-85)